<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
	<generator uri="https://dieghernan.github.io/chulapa" version="1.0.0">Chulapa</generator>
	<link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
	<link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
	<updated>2023-05-04T12:21:50-04:00</updated>
	<id>http://localhost:4000/atom.xml</id>
	<title>Quantum Secrets</title>
	
	<author>
		<name>Quantum Secrets</name>
		<uri>https://www.linkedin.com/in/schnabel/</uri>			
	</author>
	<rights>(c) 2023, Quantum Secrets</rights>
	<icon>http://localhost:4000/assets/img/quantumsecrets_logo_w.svg</icon>
	<logo>http://localhost:4000/assets/img/quantumsecrets_b_300.png</logo><entry>
		<title>Introducing Quantum Secrets</title>
		<link href="http://localhost:4000/20230428_welcome-to-quantum-secrets/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introducing Quantum Secrets"/>
		<published>2023-04-28T17:37:13-04:00</published>
		<updated>2023-04-28T17:37:13-04:00</updated>
		<id>http://localhost:4000/20230428_welcome-to-quantum-secrets/</id>
		<content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/20230428_welcome-to-quantum-secrets/">
		
  		
			&lt;img src=&#39;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1521159936751-ff7c25fd187b?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&amp;ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=crop&amp;w=987&amp;q=80&#39; &gt;
			
	&lt;p&gt;2 min.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Quantum Secrets, yet another revolutionary quantum company that came out of nowhere, has launched! We’re also launching a podcast to try to figure out the secrets behind what these other quantum companies are doing…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quantum mechanics is a fascinating branch of physics that describes the behavior of matter and energy. At Quantum Secrets, we attempt to understand and ultimately use the power of quantum mechanics to create transformative technologies that have the potential to change the world. While we haven’t really done anything yet, somehow we’re already at the forefront of every single branch of this exciting field; including quantum computing, cryptography, sensing, and imaging. We believe that the breakthroughs we make will have a profound impact on a wide range of industries, from healthcare and finance to energy and transportation. You probably shouldn’t believe us, as it’s totally unreasonable to think that any company is actually able to do all this - but we promise that we’ll prove you wrong at some undefined time in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may even try looking up who works for us on LinkedIn, but our team is a secret team that works tirelessly in stealth to push the boundaries of what’s possible in quantum technology. With decades of combined experience, we have the expertise and knowledge to take on even the most challenging problems in the field. We believe that the greatest breakthroughs in quantum technology are achieved through working together and sharing ideas, except we’re going to be pretty vague about what we’re doing for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be honest, though, we don’t really understand what most of the other quantum companies out there are actually doing. We checked out their websites, and while the marketing is getting clearer, they often leave out important details. Their academic papers are also fun to read, but don’t address whether something is practical or not in the real world. We’re kind of surprised that these companies are all actually enganging with clients; they have so many big logos on their webpages! Given the scale of the investments and valuations coming in, we’re sure that the Venture Capital community’s due diligence is validing what they’ve done with their clients, and that there aren’t any impractical limitations for near term productive use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t worry, we’re definitely not struggling to solve a problem you care about today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since our secret team is committed to unlocking the mysteries of the universe, we’re going to take a crack at understanding these other companies, too. We’re proud to be part of a community of quantum scientists and engineers who share our vision of unlocking the secrets of the universe. They’ll be open with us, as long as our approach is grounded in a commitment to collaboration, truth-seeking, and humility. Let’s just ask the leaders of these companies how they’ll overcome the apparent gaps to productive use for their technology, rather than just taking veiled potshots at them on panels. We’re going to launch the Quantum Secrets podcast to try to sort this all out and we hope you’ll join us. Let us know if you believe that a technology being commercialized has a fundamental limitations, or is way ahead of it’s time. We’ll bring in the people that can answer those questions for us all.&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
		
		<author>
			<name>Quantum Secrets</name><uri>http://localhost:4000/thequantumsecret+post@gmail.com</uri></author>
		<summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Quantum Secrets, yet another revolutionary quantum company that came out of nowhere, has launched! We’re also launching a podcast to try to figure out the secrets behind what these other quantum companies are doing…&lt;/p&gt;

</summary>
		<category term="posts"/>
		<category term="quantum-secrets"/><category term="update"/>
	</entry></feed>